gonegf.com 2019-03-19

# Privacy Policy | Gone GF

This policy covers how Gonegf.com treats personal information that Gonegf.com collects and receives in connection with your use of the Gonegf.com website and related products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

This privacy policy may be updated from time to time. We will notify you of any material changes by posting the new privacy policy on our site. You should consult this policy regularly for any changes.

INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

**General**

Gonegf.com automatically receives and records information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, Gonegf.com cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and the page you request.

Gonegf.com uses information it collects for the following general purposes: (i) to provide and improve our services, features and content, (ii) to administer your use of our services and your account, (iii) to enable users to enjoy and easily navigate our site, (iv) to better understand your needs and interests, (v) to fulfill requests you may make, (vi) to personalize your experience, (vii) to provide service announcements and notices related to comments left for you by other users, and (viii) to provide you with further information and offers from us or third parties that we believe you may find useful or interesting, including newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information on Gonegf.com related services.

**Age Restriction**

You must be at least 18 years of age to use our Site. Gonegf.com does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from individuals under 18. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personal information without their consent, he or she should contact us at privacy@Gonegf.com. If we become aware that an individual under 18 has provided us with personal information, we will delete such information from our files.

**Cookies and Log Data**

Gonegf.com may set and access Gonegf.com cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We use “persistent cookies” to save your username and login password for future logins to the Sites. We use “session ID cookies” to enable certain features of the services, to better understand how you interact with the services and to monitor web traffic routing on the site and aggregate usage of the services. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the site or all functionality of the services.

Gonegf.com uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when you visit our site. These companies may use cookies to collect information (such as which ads you have seen already or which ads you have clicked) in order to provide additional advertisements. If you would like more information and to know how to opt-out, see<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

In addition, as you use the site, our servers automatically record information that the browser sends (“Log Data”). Log Data may include, but is not limited to, your computer’s Internet Protocol address, browser type, the web page you were visiting before you came to the site and information you search for on a site.

INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE

**By Gonegf.com.**

Gonegf.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * We provide the information to partners who work on behalf of or with Gonegf.com under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information in connection with Gonegf.com’s provision of its services to you. They may also communicate with you about offers from Gonegf.com and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Gonegf.com’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
  * We transfer information about you if Gonegf.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Gonegf.com will notify you, via an announcement on our site, before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

Gonegf.com displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click targeted ads meet the targeting criteria—for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area.

  * com does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.
  * com advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies).

We may share aggregated information that includes non-identifying information with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling, and to deliver targeted advertising about other products and services. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your personal information.

**This Privacy Policy Only Applies to Gonegf.com**

This policy does not apply to the practices of people or companies that may be referenced on our site, including but not limited to advertisers, affiliates, partners, and people that Gonegf.com does not employ or manage.

LINKS TO OTHER SITES

The Gonegf.com site may contain links to other websites. If you choose to visit an advertiser by “clicking on” a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s website. The fact that we link to a website or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation that we are affiliated with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other websites and services follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.

CONFIDENTIALITY

We limit access to personal information about you to employees and contractors who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. We require all such employees and contractors to agree to protect such information.

GOVERNING LAW

This Privacy Policy is governed by the law of the State of Washington, United States of America, without regard to conflict of law principles.

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

Gonegf.com may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a prominent notice on our site.
